That
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to your own
channel Indian Stock Chart. My name is
Randeep Hooda and you are watching Chart Day
Series. Today is the date of September 1, 2001 and today is the
ninth day of four pieces. Friends,
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited is
a company related to the general insurance sector. Friends, let's
add a chat and see that the targets are
coming out, but friends, this is a one-day
chart. The stock has maintained a rise of about two and a quarter percent. The
stock closed at the upper level at
Rs. 1632.20. Now let's
see the chart for Friday. But friends, now we will
see the trend of fabric and a very
strong button is formed for fennel. But the
issue of quintal was raised. 15 is suggested
first. From there we will see the stock, it
showed a rise of about 120. And then you will see here at
1693 flight formation and inside the flat,
corner double bottom, its breakout and even now
you will see a flag being formed, that too is
quite strong, rising main, friends, it is formed.
Come friends, let's see a chat. This is
Vanmandal. Friends, you will see the trend of this top.  The
printout of the Ram Debt Consolidation of 1450 came, the shop is near Pandharaso
and you will see that there is an inverted type
formation here and in its argent a
pattern has been formed which Stark has done Sentence
obscene 15 first of all bread pile then you
will see the specific in the stock has come let's
friends let's see the chart that
friends you will see that at the same time the stock was
stuck in the rate, came out of that room, after coming out of Bigg
Boss, in this situation 14
Parmesh 1601 had also gone below Banstocks Pradesh
and you will see here it is a
round bottom formation, its do
Jaisalmer double bottom and double quote unquote Jaisalmer by
throwing the flag discus 110 016
cut it a little before and then you will
see then a writing bottom 16 ₹100
note has come let's friends let's see the chart of
one year friends you will see in that house that
those who are stuck below this 12
and you will see till now about thirteen hundred high
above  The stock was in the red,
see this and Stark had come near 12,
it was like here in an hour there was
a bullish trend in the stock, friends, it took friends
above 1500, so a good profit booking,
double roll number, then 1500 but the
bank account crossed 1600, then from there we
saw very good people, it came
below 4, and then look, it recovered, then
again below 14, and you will see
here this is a double border formation, whose
toe will automatically appear before 16,
then it is above it, but it got resistance for the
second time above 1600,
then Stark has
formed a frowning bottom, you will see it here,
which is a free website, by doing 16,
you will see here if we do a centroid
from 12, you will see here a
low formation is forming in the red, see this,
and you will see here when this pattern will
fill, there is a raised sound, so in this we call it an
ascending triangle breakout, you have a
record of ascending triangle, which is
considered to be a very bullish code.  Let's take a
look at the chart of the affair,
but friends, the trend is
absolutely positive. The staff members are
below 750 and now starting from 500, there is a
decline from there. Africa
Sure has been at ₹5000 for about 15 years. And then you will see here the
15 of the inverted hand shoulder neck line has gone
below 100 and now
you can see a record of a happy 90% triangle coming here. Let's take a
look at the chart, let's take a maximum, we will
stop and the trend is absolutely positive.
This is a long-term portfolio stock,
which you can find out its maximum from the chart.
Let's talk about it, that is
why the target in Lombard General Insurance, if
friends, if you give it a
month to two months, you will see
more than 18% gains in it.
Friends, if you like this video,
subscribe to the channel, like the videos,
share them and tell us your feedback by
writing it in the comment box. If you want to do
trading investment in the stock market,
you can contact me on my number.
If you want my service proposal
then you have to convert your funds into your demat account.
I am associated with Stars Broking Company,
but you also have the option,
you can also take my minister subscription, I
also provide portfolio management service,
account opening form,
contact number is available in the description below,
you can check it, I hope
you liked the video very much, I will
end this video here, we will meet again
with battery chart analysis, till then
friends, thank you all from the bottom of my heart.